《傑克遜大街2300號》
2300 Jackson Street
歌手：The Jacksons
時間：1989年
專輯：2300 Jackson Street
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
回想起我們的童年
Memories of growing up And working hard
在成長和努力工作中遠去
Our childhood passed us by
爸爸媽媽放棄了自己的追求
Mom and dad They sacrificed their wants and needs
為了讓我們能綻放光芒
So we could reach the light
儘管我們有時也遇到困難
Although the times were tough for us
但我們知道父母同樣辛苦
We knew they both worked hard
他們把全部心意都給了我們
They gave us all their hearts could give
隨時為愛敞開心扉
And still made room for love
我們是個集體
We're all united
緊密團結直到今天
And standing strong And still today
我們是個大家庭
We're one big family
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
永遠的家
Always home
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
永遠的家
Always home
和諧相處
In harmony, together we'll
我們手拉手的歌唱
Join hands and sing
我們的愛穿越大地
Our love across the land
記住我們一直說的，如果抓住機遇
Remember we always said, if we got a chance
要規劃我們的事業
We'll plan our work
努力實現藍圖
And work our master plan
儘管生活的道路很艱難
Although the road of life is tough
道路如此顛簸
It has it's ups and downs
我們是個整體
We are the one and all
只要在一起，我們就能克服一切
If we stay together We can conquer all
我們是個集體
We are united
緊密團結直到今天
And standing strong And still today
我們是個大家庭
We're one big family
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
永遠的家
Always home
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
不管我們走多遠
No matter how far we go
永遠的家
Always home
母親和父親
Mother and father
他們精心撫養我們才能有今天
They raised us to be The best that we could be
舞台的帷幕升起
Now the stage is set
觀眾們歡呼你的名字
The curtain's up The crowd applauds your name
向他們微笑
Then give a smile
展現你最棒的一面
Lets do you're best
不管我們走了多遠
No matter how far we go
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
永遠的家
Always home
我不會忘記你的名字，我依然如故
My friends I won't forget yout name
I'm still the same,I haven't changed
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
獻上我們的藍圖
Give in all plan
永遠的家
Always home
我永遠都能找到回家的路
I always find my way back home
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
永遠的家
Always home
傑克遜大街2300號
2300 Jackson Street
永遠的家
Always home